<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Каталог Quarriors</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Настройки</string>

    <string name="Basic_Quiddity">Сущность</string>
    <string name="Assistant">Помошник</string>
    <string name="Portal">Портал</string>
    <string name="Death_Cantrip">Колдовство Смерти</string>
    <string name="Death_Charm">Волшебство Смерти</string>
    <string name="Death_Incantation">Чары Смерти</string>
    <string name="Death_Spell">Заклинание Смерти</string>
    <string name="Growth_Cantrip">Колдовство Роста</string>
    <string name="Growth_Charm">Волшебство Роста</string>
    <string name="Growth_Incantation">Чары Роста</string>
    <string name="Growth_Spell">Заклинание Роста</string>
    <string name="Life_Cantrip">Колдовство Жизни</string>
    <string name="Life_Charm">Волшебство Жизни</string>
    <string name="Life_Incantation">Чары Жизни</string>
    <string name="Life_Spell">Заклинание Жизни</string>
    <string name="Shaping_Cantrip">Колдовство Формирования</string>
    <string name="Shaping_Charm">Волшебство Формирования</string>
    <string name="Shaping_Incantation">Чары Формирования</string>
    <string name="Shaping_Spell">Заклинание Формирования</string>
    <string name="Victory_Cantrip">Колдовство Победы</string>
    <string name="Victory_Charm">Волшебство Победы</string>
    <string name="Victory_Incantation">Чары Победы</string>
    <string name="Victory_Spell">Заклинание Победы</string>
    <string name="Deathdealer">Торговец Смертью</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Deathdealer">Могучий Торговец Смертью</string>
    <string name="Strong_Deathdealer">Сильный Торговец Смертью</string>
    <string name="Defender_of_the_Pale">Страж Границ</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Defender_of_the_Pale">Могучий Страж Границ</string>
    <string name="Strong_Defender_of_the_Pale">Сильный Страж Границ</string>
    <string name="Devotee_of_the_Holy_Query">Адепт Священного Вопроса</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Devotee_of_the_Holy_Query">Могучий Адепт Священного Вопроса</string>
    <string name="Strong_Devotee_of_the_Holy_Query">Сильный Адепт Священного Вопроса</string>
    <string name="Ghostly_Spirit">Призрак</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Ghostly_Spirit">Могучий Призрак</string>
    <string name="Strong_Ghostly_Spirit">Сильный Призрак</string>
    <string name="Primordial_Ooze">Первобытная Слизь</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Primordial_Ooze">Могучая Первобытная Слизь</string>
    <string name="Strong_Primordial_Ooze">Сильная Первобытная Слизь</string>
    <string name="Quake_Dragon">Дракон-разрушитель</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Quake_Dragon">Могучий Дракон-разрушитель</string>
    <string name="Strong_Quake_Dragon">Сильный Дракон-разрушитель</string>
    <string name="Questing_Wizard">Кудесник</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Questing_Wizard">Могучий Кудесник</string>
    <string name="Strong_Questing_Wizard">Сильный Кудесник</string>
    <string name="Scavenging_Goblin">Гоблин-мусорщик</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Scavenging_Goblin">Могучий Гоблин-мусорщик</string>
    <string name="Strong_Scavenging_Goblin">Сильный Гоблин-мусорщик</string>
    <string name="Warrior_of_the_Quay">Воитель с причала</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Warrior_of_the_Quay">Могучий Воитель с причала</string>
    <string name="Strong_Warrior_of_the_Quay">Сильный Воитель с причала</string>
    <string name="Witching_Hag">Ведьма</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Witching_Hag">Могучая Ведьма</string>
    <string name="Strong_Witching_Hag">Сильная Ведьма</string>


    <string name="Basic_Quiddity_notes_0">Card starts the game empty but as you cull these dice they
        are placed on this card and can be captured for 0 cost (although each die still uses up one
        capture for your turn).</string>
    <string name="Assistant_attributes_0">Перебрось этот кубик и любой другой</string>
    <string name="Assistant_notes_0">This is a Creature Die (official FAQ 8/15/11). If you re-roll
        another re-roll on this die, you can keep rolling this die (and potentially the same other
        die) until you don\'t get a re-roll result. It is not clear if you can choose to re-roll
        this die without re-rolling another die along with it.</string>
    <string name="Portal_attributes_0">Возьмите один кубик из вашего мешочка бросьте его</string>
    <string name="Portal_attributes_1">Возьмите два кубика из вашего мешочка бросьте их</string>
    <string name="Portal_notes_0">Portal gets placed into your used pile as soon as it is used,
        prior to drawing any dice. If your bag is empty at this point, the Portal is placed back
        into your bag with the rest of your used pile. If a situation occurs where only Portal dice
        remain in both your bag and your used pile when you use the Draw+Roll Ability, you may turn
        one Portal die to show 1 Quiddity (the inevitable result if you were to keep rolling &amp; getting more dice, official FAQ 8/15/11 ).</string>
    <string name="Death_Cantrip_attributes_0">Сотворите, чтобыдать все Существам в вашей Зоне Готовности +2 к атаке до конца хода</string>
    <string name="Death_Cantrip_attributes_1">Сотворите, чтобыдать все Существам в вашей Зоне Готовности +3 к атаке до конца хода</string>
    <string name="Death_Charm_attributes_0">Это Существо получает +3 атаке и защите</string>
    <string name="Death_Charm_attributes_1">Это Существо получает +5 атаке и защите</string>
    <string name="Death_Charm_notes_0">Must be attached on your own turn.</string>
    <string name="Death_Incantation_attributes_0">Сотворите, чтобы уничтожить 1 Существо уровня 2 или ниже</string>
    <string name="Death_Incantation_attributes_1">Сотворите, чтобы уничтожить 1 Существо любого уровня</string>
    <string name="Death_Incantation_notes_0">The casting player chooses any Creature (Level 2 or less for *) in any player\'s Ready Area. We think this can be done immediately, so it could cancel any effects that might impact the rest of your turn (for example, Mighty Defender of the Pale), but this part is unconfirmed.</string>
    <string name="Death_Spell_attributes_0">Сотворите, чтобы уничтожить 1 существо с защитой 6 или ниже в Зоне Готовности каждого вашего оппонента</string>
    <string name="Death_Spell_notes_0">The casting player chooses any Creature (defense of 6 or less) in each player\'s Ready Area. We think this can be done immediately, so it could cancel any effects that might impact the rest of your turn (for example, Mighty Defender of the Pale), but this part is unconfirmed.</string>
    <string name="Growth_Cantrip_attributes_0">Получите 2 Сущности. Вы можете захватить 1 дополнительный кубик трофеев на этом ходу</string>
    <string name="Growth_Cantrip_notes_0">Spell must be used immediately (or not used at all) and can\'t be saved until a later turn (rulebook p20).</string>
    <string name="Growth_Cantrip_notes_1">You may capture one additional Quarry die for each Growth Cantrip you cast. For example, casting 3 Growth Cantrips on a single turn would allow you to capture up to 4 Quarry dice on that turn.</string>
    <string name="Growth_Charm_attributes_0">Сотворите, т чтобы получить 3 Сущности</string>
    <string name="Growth_Charm_notes_0">Remember this can be cast now or later (and hence spent now or later)</string>
    <string name="Growth_Incantation_attributes_0">Gain 2 Quiddity. You may re-roll any 2 other dice.</string>
    <string name="Growth_Incantation_notes_0">Spell must be used immediately (or not used at all) and can\'t be saved until a later turn (rulebook p20).</string>
    <string name="Growth_Incantation_notes_1">Not clear if you can choose to re-roll only 1 other die.</string>
    <string name="Growth_Spell_attributes_0">Gain 2 Quiddity. Draw and roll 1 dice.</string>
    <string name="Growth_Spell_notes_0">Spell must be used immediately (or not used at all) and can\'t be saved until a later turn (rulebook p20).</string>
    <string name="Growth_Spell_notes_1">This die must be spent and placed in the Used Pile before a new die is drawn and rolled but you still can use the 2 Quiddity.</string>
    <string name="Growth_Spell_notes_2">Die drawn can be another "draw and roll" die (official FAQ 8/15/11).</string>
    <string name="Life_Cantrip_attributes_0">This Creature gains +4 defense.</string>
    <string name="Life_Cantrip_notes_0">Must be attached on your own turn.</string>
    <string name="Life_Charm_attributes_0">When you cast this Spell, any of your Creatures that are destroyed for the rest of the turn go to your Active Pool instead of your Used Pile.</string>
    <string name="Life_Charm_notes_0">Cast when one of your Creatures is about to die and lasts until the end of the current player\'s turn.</string>
    <string name="Life_Charm_notes_1">You will still draw 6 new dice at the beginning of your turn and roll all of your dice.</string>
    <string name="Life_Incantation_attributes_0">Cast this Spell to Reduce one Creature\'s attack to 0 (against all players) for the remainder of this turn.</string>
    <string name="Life_Incantation_notes_0">Cast to alter the attack total of another player and lasts until the end of the current player\'s turn. It is not clear if the player could still attach spells or make other changes to increase the attack value back above 0.</string>
    <string name="Life_Spell_attributes_0">Cast this Spell to give all Creatures in your Ready Area +4 defense for the remainder of this turn.</string>
    <string name="Life_Spell_notes_0">Cast when you are about to be attacked and lasts until the end of the current player\'s turn</string>
    <string name="Shaping_Cantrip_attributes_0">Cast this Spell to return one of your just destroyed Creatures to your Ready Area (at its same level) instead of putting it in the Used Pile.</string>
    <string name="Shaping_Cantrip_notes_0">Returned Creature can no longer receive damage and/or be destroyed again during the same battle (official FAQ 8/15/11) . Basically I think of it as a bystander waiting until the battle finishes at this point.</string>
    <string name="Shaping_Charm_attributes_0">Cast this Spell to rotate all Creatures in your Ready Area up 1 Level, if possible.</string>
    <string name="Shaping_Charm_notes_0">Remember the upper-left number is the Level, so a die currently has a 1 then you can rotate it to any face with a 2, or if it is a 2 you can rotate it to any face with a 3. We don\'t think you can change to a different face of the same level. We also don\'t think you can increase the level of a Strong Primordial Ooze.</string>
    <string name="Shaping_Incantation_attributes_0">When this Creature scores, you may cull one dice from your Used Pile to capture one Quarry Die that costs up to 3 Quiddity more than the dice you culled.</string>
    <string name="Shaping_Incantation_notes_0">You may cull Shaping Incantation when the spell triggers.</string>
    <string name="Shaping_Spell_attributes_0">Cast this Spell to destroy one Spell in any player\'s Ready Area.</string>
    <string name="Shaping_Spell_notes_0">If another player has a Response Spell, we think this can destroy it before it is cast, but this is unconfirmed.</string>
    <string name="Victory_Cantrip_attributes_0">This Creature gains +2 Glory when scored.</string>
    <string name="Victory_Cantrip_notes_0">Completely unconfirmed, but I think this needs to be attached on your previous turn for it to provide additional Glory when the Creature is scored.</string>
    <string name="Victory_Charm_attributes_0">Cast this Spell to gain +1 Glory for each Creature that scored this turn. You can only cast this Spell if you scored with 2 or more Creatures this turn.</string>
    <string name="Victory_Incantation_attributes_0">Cast this Spell to gain +3 Glory.</string>
    <string name="Victory_Spell_attributes_0">Cast this Spell to gain +1 Glory for each opponent that had a Creature destroyed by one of your attacks this turn (maximum 1 Glory per player attacked). You can only cast this Spell after your attack phase.</string>
    <string name="Deathdealer_attributes_0">When Deathdealer scores, you may trade Deathdealer for one dice from any other player\'s Used Pile.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Deathdealer_attributes_0">The first time a Creature is destroyed while Deathdealer is attacking an opponent, increase your attack total against that player by Deathdealer\'s attack. Use this ability only once per attack, per player. (This increase is not cumulative, start each attack against each player with your original attack value).</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Deathdealer_notes_0">It is clear that if you destroy more than one Creature the attack increase only happens once, but it is not clear whether you can use this ability twice if you have two Mighty Deathdealers (do both add their attack back on the first destroyed creature?).</string>
    <string name="Strong_Deathdealer_attributes_0">When you Destroy a Creature, immediately score Deathdealer (place it in your Used Pile). This does not reduce your attack total for the turn.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Deathdealer_notes_0">This happens whether or not Deathdealer was needed for the attack. It is not clear whether you get to cull a die as a result of this scoring.</string>
    <string name="Defender_of_the_Pale_attributes_0">When Defender of the Pale scores, you earn 1 additional Glory for each other Creature that scores this turn.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Defender_of_the_Pale_attributes_0">Your opponents must spend 1 additional Quiddity to summon each Creature as long as Defender of the Pale is in your Ready Area.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Defender_of_the_Pale_attributes_1">Your opponents must spend 2 additional Quiddity to summon each Creature as long as Defender of the Pale is in your Ready Area.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Defender_of_the_Pale_notes_0">For example: If you have a Quaxos Scavenging Goblin with 2 defense (+1 defense for the other Quaxos in play for a total of 3) and an Assistant (with defense 2) and you are attacked by a Quaxos Quake Dragon with 5 damage - you may only assign 3 damage to the Scavenging Goblin - the final 2 damage must be assigned to the Assistant. In this case, the Scavenging Goblin would survive while the Assistant would be destroyed. Remember that your Quaxos defender can only absorb damage up to its defense, but if any of that damage is from a Quaxos attacker, your defender will not be destroyed.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Defender_of_the_Pale_notes_1">Even a Creature that is "free" to summon costs additional (e.g. Quaxos’ Warrior of the Quay\'s ability) (official FAQ 8/15/11). We think these costs are cumulative so if multiple copies of this Creature are in Ready Areas the cost may be increased even more.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Defender_of_the_Pale_attributes_0">When Defender of the Pale scores, draw 1 additional die and add it to your Active Pool.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Defender_of_the_Pale_attributes_1">When Defender of the Pale scores, draw 2 additional dice and add them to your Active Pool.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Defender_of_the_Pale_notes_0">You draw the die before you have a chance to cull your dice, so this may cause you to empty your Used Pile and leave fewer choices for culling (unconfirmed) .</string>
    <string name="Strong_Defender_of_the_Pale_notes_1">When drawing dice for scoring the Strong Defender of the Pale and your bag is empty, the Strong Defender of the Pale is placed into the used pile and included when you fill your bag from your used pile before drawing.</string>
    <string name="Devotee_of_the_Holy_Query_attributes_0">Devotee of the Holy Query gains +2 defense.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Devotee_of_the_Holy_Query_attributes_0">Devotee of the Holy Query gains +3 defense. When you attack with Devotee of the Holy Query, ignore the effects of all Spells attached to opposing creatures. Devotee of the Holy Query can\'t be the target of opposing Spells.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Devotee_of_the_Holy_Query_attributes_0">When Devotee of the Holy Query scores, you may capture one Spell Die that costs 4 Quiddity or less for free. Add that Spell Die to your bag.</string>
    <string name="Ghostly_Spirit_attributes_0">When Ghostly Spirit is destroyed, you may cull 1 Basic Quiddity Die to return Ghostly Spirit to your Ready Area (for free).</string>
    <string name="Ghostly_Spirit_notes_0">Assumed (but not verified) that the culled die would come from your Used Pile.</string>
    <string name="Ghostly_Spirit_notes_1">Returned at the same Level (official FAQ 8/15/11).</string>
    <string name="Ghostly_Spirit_notes_2">Returned Creature can no longer receive damage and/or be destroyed again during the same battle (official FAQ 8/15/11) .</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Ghostly_Spirit_attributes_0">When Ghostly Spirit is destroyed, set Ghostly Spirit aside until you destroy any Creature. Then roll the Ghostly Spirit: If you roll a Creature Icon, add it to your Ready Area (for free). Otherwise, add Ghostly Spirit to your Used Pile.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Ghostly_Spirit_notes_0">Assumed (but not verified) that if added back to the Ready Area it would not add to your attack value because Step 1 of "Attack Your Rivals" has already passed, but would score if it survives until your next turn.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Ghostly_Spirit_attributes_0">When Ghostly Spirit is destroyed, add Ghostly Spirit to your Active Pool.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Ghostly_Spirit_notes_0">You will still draw 6 new dice at the beginning of your turn and roll all of your dice.</string>
    <string name="Primordial_Ooze_attributes_0">\? = The number of Basic Quiddity Dice in your Used Pile and Active Pool (combined). If you have no Basic Quiddity Dice in play, Primordial Ooze is destroyed.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Primordial_Ooze_attributes_0">\? = The number of Creatures in all Ready Areas.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Primordial_Ooze_notes_0">Assumed (but not verified) that your attack value is calculated immediately when you start the attack and only once (even if you kill some other enemies) because Step 1 of "Attack Your Rivals" has already passed, but would score if it survives until your next turn. Assumed the defense value is determined each time the Ooze is attacked.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Primordial_Ooze_attributes_0">Primordial Ooze exactly copies one Creature in any of your opponents\' Ready Areas (your choice). If no other Creatures are in play, Primordial Ooze has attack 0 and defense 5. You may change the Creature being copied once during each player\'s turn.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Primordial_Ooze_notes_0">When the ooze enters the Ready area (by any means) - you must copy a creature in an opponents\' area, if able. It copies another creature exactly including its glory (the 2 Glory is there only if there are no other creatures to copy). If the copied creature then goes away it does not impact the ooze as it remains the creature it copied. Attached spells are not copied. An ooze can copy an ooze that copied another creature (and thus becomes that originally copied creature). Once it has copied a creature it cannot shift back to just an ooze (unless it’s copying another "plain" ooze in an opponents\' ready area). Spells or affects that return the Ooze to the ready area make the ooze have to copy a new creature or be 0/5. Once in the used pile (after all scoring/spell affects have occurred) or if you roll/reroll the die and immediate affects are resolved it loses all memory of previous states.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Primordial_Ooze_notes_1">If the ooze has copied a creature (like the ghostly spirits) that have an ability that continues after it is destroyed it remains a copy of that creature until it is returned to the ready area, used pile or rolled and any immediate affects resolved of the creature it was copying (Ex. an Ooze has copied a Mighty Ghostly Spirit. It is destroyed. Once you destroy a creature you roll the copied Mighty Ghostly Spirit and either add it to your ready area or used pile, after this point it is an “ooze” die with no memory of what came before). (official FAQ 8/15/11)</string>
    <string name="Strong_Primordial_Ooze_notes_2">It is not clear whether you have an opportunity to change the copied creature on your turn right before scoring. I do think it copies the Level of the other Creature. The default values of 0/5 are only available right when the Creature is summoned and only if no opponents have Creatures in their Ready Areas.</string>
    <string name="Quake_Dragon_attributes_0">Destroy all Level 1 Creatures in your opponent\'s Ready Area when you attack with Quake Dragon (before your opponent chooses a defender).</string>
    <string name="Quake_Dragon_attributes_1">Quake Dragon has no additional ability.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Quake_Dragon_attributes_0">Quake Dragon gains +1 defense.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Quake_Dragon_attributes_1">Quake Dragon gains +2 defense and you earn +2 Glory when it scores.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Quake_Dragon_attributes_0">Creatures that are Level 2 or less cannot attack you as long as Quake Dragon is in your Ready Area (do not add their attack value to the attack total).</string>
    <string name="Strong_Quake_Dragon_attributes_1">Quake Dragon has no additional ability.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Quake_Dragon_notes_0">May require you to recalculate your attack value for each defending player.</string>
    <string name="Questing_Wizard_attributes_0">You may draw and roll one additional die and re-roll Questing Wizard (instead of gaining Quiddity).</string>
    <string name="Questing_Wizard_attributes_1">Questing Wizard gains +1 defense and you earn +1 Glory when it scores.</string>
    <string name="Questing_Wizard_notes_0">The "Draw &amp; Roll + 1 Quiddity" face does require you to "spend" this die and put it into your Used Pile but you still receive the 1 Quiddity to spend.</string>
    <string name="Questing_Wizard_notes_1">I think you can use this action even if you can\'t draw another die (effectively just re-rolling this die)</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Questing_Wizard_attributes_0">When Questing Wizard scores, all Quarry Dice cost you 2 less Quiddity to capture this turn, and you may capture 1 additional Quarry die this turn.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Questing_Wizard_attributes_1">You may spend Questing Wizard as an Immediate Effect to draw and roll 2 dice from your bag (instead of gaining Quiddity).</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Questing_Wizard_attributes_2">Questing Wizard has no additional ability.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Questing_Wizard_notes_0">You may capture one additional Quarry Die for each Mighty Questing Wizard that scores. For example, scoring with 3 Mighty Questing Wizards on a single turn would allow you to capture up to 4 Quarry dice on that turn with a discount of 6 per die (unconfirmed).</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Questing_Wizard_notes_1">The "Draw &amp; Roll + 1 Quiddity" face does require you to "spend" this die and put it into your Used Pile but you still receive the 1 Quiddity to spend.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Questing_Wizard_attributes_0">When Questing Wizard scores, you may cull any number of Spell Dice from your Active Pool or Ready Area for 1 Glory each (even if they were not attached to Questing Wizard).</string>
    <string name="Strong_Questing_Wizard_attributes_1">Questing Wizard has no additional ability.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Questing_Wizard_notes_0">In most cases, when you score at the beginning of your turn, your Active Pool will be empty although your Ready Area may have spells you have saved from earlier turns.</string>
    <string name="Scavenging_Goblin_attributes_0">Gain +1 Quiddity when you summon Scavenging Goblin.</string>
    <string name="Scavenging_Goblin_notes_0">The Quiddity gained when summoning the Scavenging Goblin may be used to either summon additional Creatures, or to capture Quarry dice. You only summon the creature on your turn by paying the proper Quiddity cost.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Scavenging_Goblin_attributes_0">When Scavenging Goblin is destroyed, draw 2 dice and add them to your Active Pool.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Scavenging_Goblin_notes_0">If your bag is empty when Mighty Scavenging Goblin is destroyed, it is placed into the bag before drawing.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Scavenging_Goblin_attributes_0">Scavenging Goblin gains +1 defense for each other Creature in your Ready Area.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Scavenging_Goblin_notes_0">It seems that as other Creatures are destroyed in a battle, Strong Scavenging Goblin immediately loses the associated bonus for the rest of the combat (unconfirmed) .</string>
    <string name="Warrior_of_the_Quay_attributes_0">Warrior of the Quay gains +3 attack if the defending player has only 1 Creature in his Ready Area.</string>
    <string name="Warrior_of_the_Quay_notes_0">Evaluated for each defending player, so the +3 attack only impacts players that have only 1 Creature in their Ready Area.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Warrior_of_the_Quay_attributes_0">When Warrior of the Quay is summoned, all other Warriors of the Quay in al other players\' Ready Areas are immediately destroyed. You may only summon one Warrior of the Quay per turn.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Warrior_of_the_Quay_attributes_0">All other Creatures in your Ready Area get +1 attack and +1 defense as long as Warrior of the Quay is in your Ready Area</string>
    <string name="Strong_Warrior_of_the_Quay_notes_0">Includes other Warriors of the Quay, so if you had a total of 3 in your Ready Area, each Warrior of the Quay would get +2 attack and +2 defense from the other two dice.</string>
    <string name="Witching_Hag_attributes_0">You gain +1 Quiddity for each Creature you destroy as long as Witching Hag is in your Ready Area.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Witching_Hag_attributes_0">As long as Witching Hag is in your Ready Area, all Creatures with an attack value higher than 3 that attack you have their attack reduced to 3.</string>
    <string name="Mighty_Witching_Hag_notes_0">Only applies when you have the Mighty Witching Hag and you are being attacked. Multiple instances do not have additional impact. Even if attacker has bonus strength, each attacking Creature only has an attack value of 3.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Witching_Hag_attributes_0">When Witching Hag scores, you may move 1 other Creature Die from your Used Pile to your Active Pool.</string>
    <string name="Strong_Witching_Hag_notes_0">A Creature Die is any die that has at least one Creature face on it (which face is showing while in the Used Pile has no impact).</string>
    <string name="Strong_Witching_Hag_notes_1">Can select another Creature Die that just scored in the same turn (official FAQ 8/15/11).</string>

</resources>